so it is week 11 of trying to turn one
of these $100 into a million dollars and
something has happened in this video and
you guys are going to see at the end of
of how I actually blew the
$300,000 in one single week I made such
a simple mistake but this mistake I
compounded it and ended up blowing the
account let me show you guys exactly
what happened this week and how I blew
basically 12 weeks of work that I took
into this
challenge
all right so we're going to start off
this week so this week I had to do
everything with the red pen on the
picture I don't think I don't think I've
shown the picture so let me show you
guys I usually write it with a black p
so come here so you guys can see right
here every single week I do like week
one week two week 3 week four 5 6 7 8 n
and then week 10 which I just realized
that week nine is our first week W so
we've been on a 9 we winning
streak week 10 we lost so that means
that this is week 11 so I had to pull
out the red Market to draw the [__]
red losing week but this week we're
going to come back you know it's part of
the process my longest winning streak
has been 14 weeks and now I almost beat
it but let's get back into the markets
to see how we're going to make it back
this week so let me show you guys before
anything this is how we currently are on
the account so we're up about
254,000 so if I show you guys this week
we have Bitcoin obviously we've been
predicting Bitcoin Longs for quite some
time you guys can just go to the
previous video waiting for the retest
here to then buy this is my entry signal
where I wanted to get in here but I
didn't get into Bitcoin I just you know
I'm looking at it for long-term purposes
next for my number one pair for the week
we have Euro AUD Euro AUD is very simple
this is the trade that we lost last week
we got Wicked out and then price pretty
much kept going to the downside so this
is where I'm waiting for price to then
retest this level of support support
support support to then sell so we've
barely made it to that zone right there
like barely so I'm going to wait for
price to actually get into there in
order for us to be able to sell it so if
you notice I just put an alarm so it
notifies us once we get there in order
for it to go to the downside next is
audjpy so we've taken this trade many
times in this series many times as a
whole with my trading strategy we have
three time frames in sync weekly daily
4our and then I'm just going to be
waiting for a retest of this zone right
here to go long has round psychological
level 95500 we go to the weekly time
frame we're going to be retesting weekly
structure points as well so this is a
very simple very easy trade and then if
I go down to the 4our the 4 Hour we're
going to be retesting the 4our EMA
nzdjpy is the next pair and this one is
very similar it's like the cousin of
audjpy weekly is bullish daily is
bullish 4 hours bullish so the only
thing that makes sense is to buy so we
have to wait for this retest of this
area here to then go long so if you
notice this is a pullback to then head
to the upside we're going to wait for
our alarm to get hit in order to enter
this trade and then if you notice that
pool pull back is going to retest our
weekly structure point if we go down to
the 4our we're going to also be
retesting the 4our EMA at that area of
Interest next we have AUD CAD which we
were selling for a very long time but
now the time frames have shifted so now
the daily is bullish and then the 4our
is bullish but the weekly time frame is
bearish so we do have to keep in mind
that we have to be looking for buys as a
day trade so that's where I'm going to
be waiting for this price to pull back
into here retest result resistance
support support support support so we
retest it and then head to the upside
and then last but not least is going to
be GBP CAD but this is like a big swing
Traders you're going to wait for price
to pull back up into here so might be
information overload but it's very
simple so make sure you guys pay
attention you guys put down the pairs
obviously you guys are going to see this
already once it's recorded but we're
going to check up either later tonight
in London or if not tomorrow in the
morning once and if we are able to catch
one of these trades so I'll check up
with you guys in a little bit all right
guys good morning so it is Monday
morning so I might you know I don't look
like I'm in my office off currently
right now in Bickle so my house right
now is going through some Renovations
also the bathrooms we clocks just some
things are getting fixed and we're not
looking good on the challenge right now
we are down pretty bad I went higher
risk than I ever expected um I'm not
going to lie this is happens to me every
single time I trade out of my
environment whenever I'm not in my
office and I do what I'm supposed to
like follow my routine and just do
everything the same the same the same
the same exact thing always happens so
yeah we're not looking good right now so
this is how we're currently looking
right now so we already took one loss it
hit our stop loss and now we're
currently in job on about 40K so as you
guys can see this is AUD JPY so it's the
trade that we took I'm not going to lie
I would have never taken this trade this
fast but you know since you know I
wasn't in the house I mean not not
giving excuses the point is that I took
a trade that I wasn't supposed to take I
could have waited for a little bit more
confluences but exactly what I expected
the price to come back pull back to this
area retest structure uh if you go down
into the daily we're retesting the daily
structure I just got in way too high I
should be getting in right now at the
bottom here but the reason why I got in
is because I see this beautiful 1 hour
bullish and golfing and after that I'm
all right guys we're going to get it
Sunday we're going to make back last
week's profits plus you know make more
and then I didn't realize that I was
buying straight into resistance I was
buying Under the EMA as soon as I bought
last night literally at London session
you guys know I trade London for the
challenge 3: in the morning price is
going straight down so I took multiple
trades all of them where I had the same
take profit but the scalings I had
different stop losses the middle one
already hit stop loss and these other
two right now they're crazy about to hit
stop loss right now so currently how we
are on the challenge right now
everything else basically is remaining
the same Euro AUD We Are retesting The
Zone but I didn't want to sell cuz we're
above that strong level of support the
only way I can sell is if we are under
that level of support So once we are
under that level of support then I could
be interested in selling um this is
crazy nzdjpy we still haven't made it to
the area of Interest so I'm waiting for
it to come here in order for me to enter
the trade for for a buy and then AUD CAD
we have retested this Zone but damn man
I got distracted with the other one bro
so this how we're currently looking
right now on a cat so we'll keep you
guys updated we got a wait for AUD JPY
to play out and I'm not the type of
person to ever give excuses but like
damn for the one day that I step out of
my house the one day that I decid to you
know Le trade London on a Sunday bro it
is what it is we're going to come back
from this and I'll keep you guys up so
stop loss officially hit on the account
a couple hours ago I just decided to
kind of take the day off and just not
pretty much be connected to the charts
uh I really did overtrade I greed God to
me and stop loss officially hit on the
account let me actually just show you
guys so currently right now we're up
well technically down to 183,000 you
guys can see all three positions here
hit stop loss pretty aggressive I could
have been very patient and just waited
for the trade in order for us to take it
um I do still like the trade in order
for me to take this trade I would pretty
much I would have to be waiting for a
break and then a retest like this to go
long I haven't been you know stopped out
on a trade this fast in a while the
emotions definitely got to me also not
being kind of in my home I'm pretty much
here BR like view is nice but I'm just
not in what I'm used to but I am eyeing
up Euro AUD for potential sales so I
kind of threw up this RIS reward ratio
earlier this morning after that bearish
engulfing if you notice that's at 10:00
as soon as I got stopped out but I
decided I Y I got to step away can't be
emotional because just just can't happen
in this challenge next we have nzdjpy
which is my interest as well I have to
wait for it to make it all the way to
the area right there so I can take the
trade long and then next we have AUD CAD
which is retesting the Zone exactly how
you want in order to take the trade to
the upside so I'm going to be waiting on
that oh obviously like like all this
noise you know I'm not in my home bro
like I I can't put the blame on that uh
the blame is just I didn't follow my
plan I got greedy broke my rules and it
is what it is so now I'm going to see if
we I can get some some of these solid
trades make back the losses and we keep
this challenge going so currently right
now so it is currently Monday 6:43 in
the afternoon so daily Candlestick just
closed and let's just see what happens
for the rest of the day all right guys
the market update it's currently about
to be 1:00 in the morning right now uh
Monday night so technically Tuesday
morning so we just got stopped out from
Air Euro AUD textbook trade we just
about to get stopped out right now on
AUD Cad and I'm telling you this happens
to me time and time again when I don't
have my routine right I'm not putting
the blame on anybody but this just shows
you have to follow your routine
um almost down 100k right now on from
where the starting badage was let me let
me just show you guys so we took about a
$27,000 loss on Euro aded and we're
currently about to get stopped out on
AUD CAD so that would leave us at about
136k on the account if you guys can see
Euro AUD we've taken this trade 100
times this is the 4-Hour time frame
we're retesting support support support
being used as resistance this is the 1
hour time frame if I go down to now that
I mean now if I go down to the 1 hour we
have the shift the structure we have 1
hour bearish engulfing Evening Star
formation rejection from the structure
literally perfect exactly what we did
here if anything even cleaner but
obviously here headed to the downside
here it did not so if I see this trade
again I will take a time and time and
time and time again this just happens to
be one of those times where it doesn't
play out and then currently right now
AUD CAD is the same exact break and
retest so we broke to the upside we went
bullish we retested this extremely
strong level of support support support
supports right here this is currently
the 4H hour when I went down to the 1
hour this is where I saw my entry signal
right at that area of interest you can
see the 1H hour dogee not the strongest
entry signal but it's a solid
confirmation we have a 30 minute morning
start formation followed with a 30
minute dogee rejection Candlestick and
straight into draw down I put my stop
loss very strategically under this next
level of support and resistance clearly
a level of resistance support and then
and supported over here as well
so yeah just part of the process
honestly you know luckily we had some
stops on audjpy keep heading it kept
heading to the downside so this is why
you put a stop loss this one is just
insane and this one just looks like
we're about to get stopped out so you
know at least you know good thing we
have a dope view doing this from
crickle just sucks man this is annoying
what's up guys so it is the next morning
my bad for all the noise we're here in
the like the city there's a lot of noise
in the city
I woke up I feel a lot better and I just
needed some rest and uh currently right
now it is 10:00 in the morning on
Tuesday and you know I pretty much
reflected throughout the night and in
the morning I I've just been impatient
I've had fomo and I've had a lot of
grief like you guys have to kind of you
know imagine the time that I put into
this and I just want to complete it
already right I could be doing so many
other things that could be focusing on
other projects even personally myself so
I I think I decided that today I'm not
going to trade anymore I don't want to
do I don't want to stop trading for the
week because last week I completely
missed a lot of Market opportunities
when I stopped trading for the week so I
might just stop trading today as a whole
just to refresh and then we come back
you know tonight during London so let me
show you guys the market opportunity
that I'm waiting for them to line up so
I take currently looking about
134 crazy we lost about 100,000 and
under 24 hours so first trade setup is
Euro ad so obviously if this daily kind
is to close above what I'm going to be
waiting for is I'm going to be waiting
for this retest right here to retest EMA
retest structure and then we'll take
this trade to the upside next trade
setup that I'm waiting on is
nzdjpy this one is actually going to be
ready for today but I'm going to try my
best to just stay out of it even though
it's a very solid opportunity we're
coming to retesting daily structure we
go down to the 4H hour we're also
retesting for our structure I would want
to take this trade want to be break and
retest above the EMA and above support
or resistance audjpy I was completely
wrong cuz why you need a stop loss
completely you know just ran through our
stop loss and then a cad as well is why
you have to use the stop loss so going
to be waiting on these trade setups to
uh line up and yeah I just you know
enjoy the view and honestly like like I
was just thinking earlier this morning
so I'm like well you know if like this
account gets blown I just do it again
right I'm just more of stress of the
time that I've put into it but I'm
realizing I'm like yo like bro you got
money set aside you make money from a
bunch of other things like you know
let's just do this for the people if the
account gets blown so I I'm no longer in
the mindset scared to lose the like I'm
not scared to blow the account if it if
it gets blown it is what it is it's
really part of the process of f risking
33% of the account so uh if it gets
blown we'll just do it again honestly so
I'm going to stay focused today keep
that clear mindset that I've you know
fil throughout now this morning and then
I'll update you guys later throughout
the day so despite us losing a little
bit over 100k in under 24 hours good
thing we still have the cars owned
outright cash so this thing's Beast that
Wing is
crazy good thing we own these things
cash so we're good keep how that opens
up cold well never
mind said I forgot what's up guys good
morning so the one night I decide to
fall asleep during London or not even
that I decide I just happened to to lay
down and I knocked out and I woke up and
this thing is just gone is the night
where this happens perfectly and it
could have not happened in a worse week
and this shows you that in trading
things are going to constantly happen to
you like this time and time and time and
time and time again which they almost
seem like perfect failures set in your
direction perfect things that happen
that aren't in your favor and it's just
part of the journey there just things
that are going to happen you're going to
get Wicked out that one time you risk a
little bit more you're going to get
stopped out that one time that you put
your stop loss where it wasn't supposed
to be you're going to hit a loss when
you decide to trade news when you've
never traded news and there's also going
to be sometimes where you risk a little
bit more and then the trade goes to your
take profit super fast and you know it's
just part of obviously life we all know
this is a bunch of like such weird
coincidence that happened at the
craziest timings that this just happens
to be one of them right now so let me
show you guys um where we are right now
so this is AUD CAD we had a beautiful
I'm talking about beautiful left head
head right shoulder uh rejection from
this level of support 4our morning start
formation literally everything I look
for in a trade basically exactly what
we're looking for here but even better
because we had higher time frame
rejections I explained this all
throughout my social media you guys can
see here this is my Instagram and you
guys can see that's up there that says
12 hours ago I literally said loading so
let me go back one story
loading loading and then look at that
the one night that I follow asleep so
this is posted 12 minutes ago and all
these were 10 hours ago so I mean it is
what it is you know that you you can't
you can't do anything this is just part
of the process so now I'm what I'm going
to be doing is I'm going to be waiting
for a little pullback to then continue
heading to the upside Euro ad we never
managed to make it to the area of
Interest so no trade here nzd JPY we
have now shifted the market structure
clearly this Market is now bearish along
with the daily time frame now being
bearish so I'm going to be waiting for a
retest here here to then head to the
downside we are no longer interested in
buys and this is a prime example of how
the market can switch extremely fast so
you have to learn how to react and adapt
to it AUD JPY same thing we were bullish
and now we are bearish this daily has
pretty much engulfed a lot of price in
just one single day uh AUD CAD is the
one that we just explained GBP CAD we
are heading up to the area of Interest
right now so we still have some time to
wait for there so this is currently
where the account is right now where we
are sitting at
134,000 and it is currently right now
let me just show you guys it is
currently right
now Wednesday 9 in the morning so we're
going to see if we could catch some of
these trades coming very very soon all
right guys good morning so it is
currently Thursday 10:00 in the morning
so I'm just laughing because like all
the markets right I predict the
direction pretty much the majority of
the time right but then there's
sometimes where I pick the wrong one so
let's say I have four markets and I pick
uh three of them are going to go up
one's going to go down and out of those
four markets three are winners once a
loss I picked the loss and it is what it
is you know what I mean you can't do
anything about it I understand this is
the part of trading and I understand
that this will never not change and
there's nothing you can do to avoid this
right the Market's always going to do
whatever it does but today is just one
of those days so let me let me just show
you guys so this was earlier this
morning because I was just catching it
for the Instagram live and then if you
guys can see literally nzd JPY stopped
us out and then I ended up closing at
the high point right there cuz I didn't
want it to hit my stop loss I didn't
follow my rules I didn't set and forget
so this is a trade that I explained last
night that we were looking for the break
and retest to then buy but then I can
see some sell opportunities because
we're rejecting under this very strong
structure point we have rejection from
this daily structure Point everything
that I would want in a trade is pretty
much there but damn I mean it is like
like I I say this all the time it is
what it is there's nothing that I could
do so I'm going to wait for now as a
little quick break retest under to then
sell AUD JPY never got the trade Euro
AUD we missed this trade yesterday this
trade had pulled back perfectly to the
area that I anticipated but then we had
the 1H hour Morning Star formation under
the area of Interest so I can only take
a trade if we are above a Zone as you
guys can see if we go to the left
whenever we're under we're selling
whenever we're above we're buying and in
this case we were under and when broke
above we never retested it you guys know
I always need for price to then break
the area and then retest it so it can go
up never retested it so it was never
able to cat the trade and then AUD CAD
which is a total monster has completely
left without me the trade was perfectly
at this area this trade would have made
back loads of profits
and literally everything crazy um but
yeah currently right now we're sitting
on the accounts at
99,100 and 21 so I and forget so market
update it is currently right now
midnight getting ready for war tonight
so it is the last day of the week Friday
or it's technically the last Le session
of the week and I'm I'm ready like I'm
just going all in whatever happens
happens and this will be the day either
I come out on top today or we blow the
account tonight so I'm going to show you
guys what I have lined up for tonight so
we won't be needing this tonight no
position guy's calculator so let's get
started so Euro AUD I'm going to be
looking for Longs we have pulled back to
our area of Interest we are retesting
here retesting EMA so I'm going to be
looking for buys at this area going to
be waiting for any bullish engulfing any
rejection candlesticks looks like we're
getting that as of right now so it's
looking very solid that's why it's my
number one pair as of right now nzdjpy
luckily we closed our losses early like
we cut our losses early cuz if not this
would have pretty much blown the account
so we cut it around somewhere on this
area here which avoided us a huge loss
next we have uh well to finish off on
this trade I'm just going to be waiting
for a pull back to then take the trade
long next we have audjpy which I'm going
to be waiting for it to dip into this
area right here round psychological
level one uh my bad uh
95,000 which're is going to be retesting
structure structure and EMA so around
psychological level when I'm going to be
waiting for rejections of this level
around here to then take the trade short
next we have have AUD CAD which has just
been again once again a monster it's
just pretty much left from the area of
Interest left head right shoulder we are
technically still not above the neckline
of The Head and Shoulders we have to
break above this point right here so if
you can even see it on the daily left
head right shoulder so this is can also
be a very solid trade setup for next
week where we can be waiting for this
easy break retest to then head to the
upside we're going to retest the neck
line retest round psychological level
87500 and retest Eman structure so it
looks very very solid so these are the
setups that I have as of right now so as
you guys can see it is currently Friday
midnight so I'm
ready all right good morning guys so
we're officially be the account we're
about to hit Margin Call right now um
[__] man because like I literally
predicted EUR AUD I predicted all these
other pairs but just because of the
emotion because of the greed because I
missed the other was and I didn't catch
him I forced this trade I didn't even
know there was news going down right now
and [__] bro let me just show you guys
so this is how we're currently looking
on the account right now we took the
adad buys and they weren't terrible buys
but I had explained to you guys
yesterday how we had to wait for the
break and retest we had to wait for the
break and retest of the neckline of The
Head and Shoulders this is literally
what we've been waiting on this is what
the whole point of the S foret strategy
is I've just been getting greedy you
emotional because for example trades
like this one like Euro AUD I predicted
them perfectly we had the pull back to
the area rejected we had the pull back
again and then we rejected didn't enter
the trade everything that I've been
explaining has been happening perfect
this is pulling back
audjpy has pulled back to the area of
Interest like I explained 95,000 we
rejected the EMA look at that beautiful
rejection
Candlestick and I just decided to force
this trade bro just because I wasn't
involved in any other markets man bro
and this is just thrown out as I'm
literally recording this oh my God and
you want what I just realized cuz I'm
going through the Discord of all the
community members bro this is NFP the
news have completely got to me it is the
first Friday of the month and I had
absolutely no
idea wow wow wow wow we have officially
blown the account that is crazy 2 and
1/2 months 3 months just down the drain
in one [__]
week wow all right so that's all for
this video and like it kind of sucks
because I've been I feel like I'm almost
like I've been building this baby or
building this project of this account
for almost 3 months now and it just gets
taken away from me I I lose it in in a
matter of One Week by some simple
mistake that I did and I knew I was
making the mistake but I was so lost in
the moment I was just blinded by my
emotions and I realized that the mistake
that I did was it was me it was the the
way I was handling the situation and it
caused me to pretty much throw out 300K
out the window caused me to throw out 3
months out the window and I'm here
telling you guys the truth of how I feel
and I'm accepting full uh responsibility
for what happened that's why I'm here in
this dark mode right now you know it's
pretty ironic cuz I blew 300K and I just
rented this you know 2 acre Villa and I
been here for 2 weeks now so it's pretty
ironic how I literally just blew 300K
and I'm here but you know obviously
that's trailer lifestyle but it's really
not about the money that was lost it's
about the time and the mistakes that
were made because the mistakes that I
made were simply just because of me and
uh what I have to say is that this isn't
the end of it there's more to come and
if you guys want to know more about what
this dark mode consist of and how I'm
getting better and how I'm going to come
back even stronger make sure you guys
stay tuned and hit the Subscribe button
because there's going to be another
video of exactly what I'm doing and how
going to come back even harder so
appreciate you guys watching all the way
to the end hope you guys could you know
learn from my lessons and I'll see you
guys in the next video